hey hello everybody and welcome to my
from scratch to bond challenge now I
know this has been done by a couple
other YouTubers but I thought it'd be
fun to give it a shot and see how long
it takes me to go from an account with
no stats absolutely no money like look
at my bank I literally have nothing and
uh yeah try to get to a bond uh with
only free topl uh money-making methods
or freeo playay content or how someone
could go about getting a bond
from scratch so we're going to set a
timer for 24 hours now hopefully it
won't take me that long but yeah we'll
keep a timer going uh the only time
we're going to stop the timer is if I
have no offers in the grand exchange and
I'm logged out if there's offers in the
grand exchange then I have to wait till
they're done or I can't stop the timer
uh because that wouldn't really be fair
but I'm not going to try hard it for 17
hours in a row uh cuz I'm not crazy
anyway let's start the timer and begin
all right so the first step to this very
long Quest is to get some money now it
doesn't have to be much money now I went
to go try to kill Goblin and literally
just got wrecked so I decided and
realized I might as well just pick some
stuff up at the Grand exchange uh cuz I
can go sell that for easily enough money
uh to start buying from the shops in vck
and that is my initial plan and you may
notice this is more of a kind of live
commentary uh whereas some of the other
from zero to bond episodes have been
kind of a very quick uh dub Steppy
compilation no commentary so I thought
I'd make mine a little bit different
explain a little bit more what I'm doing
what my plans are so what I'm planning
on doing is first Gathering up some
ashes and then we're going to go uh sell
that to the Grand exchange and uh
hopefully afford some items there uh
that we can sell uh for a decent amount
of profit once we have maybe a couple
thousand gold uh we'll go ahead and go
into the Wilderness the plan is to buy
some team capes uh which hopefully we
can sell for a couple ,000 each uh we
have to go deep into the Wilderness for
that and uh yeah that's all I really
have thought out so far but we'll come
up with some good ideas and yeah that's
well we'll see how much we can at least
sell this for uh we don't need a lot of
gold to begin with here just a
bit okay 196 gold that's fine sure we'll
sell The Jug why
not and the pot so that will leave us
with about 200 gold that's perfect
enough to start with and we'll move on
to the next method if you call on method
anyway okay so like I said our plan is
to buy uh from some shops in verac and
now one of the better shops you can do
with a very low cash stack is uh tsa's
fine clothes I guess you would pronounce
it we're going to buy out stuff like the
brown apron you can see it only costs
two coins from the shop could sell
upwards of 580 coins I'll buy the blue
skirts which sell
for uh
297 uh we could buy maybe the presin
down five coins from the store and
inactive might not go for that one uh
aprons probably would sell quickly only
50 coins each and red capes uh go for
150 each we'll buy The Capes out and all
we're going to do from there is just hop
world we'll go ahead uh just use all our
cash up and then uh we'll sell it and
maybe repeat it at least one time we're
looking for about 2 to 5K uh before we
head into the Wilderness and buy out the
team capes
all right so we spent all our money and
uh we're back at the Grand exchange now
I'm going to be kind of surprised that I
think this actually decently profitable
now the uh Brown a and uh the blue skirt
seem to sell for quite a bit so we'll go
ahead and pop one of these in here and
see what insta sells for and uh we're
just going to sell
one and see what it sells for see if it
sells at all 4 50 uh that is okay with
me we'll go pop those in there for 450
see how many we manage to
sell all of them wow uh we might
actually do that a bit longer then
because that is not bad money per hour
for free to play assuming an offer is
still in there uh put the red cape in
did not sell and the blue
skirt see what this sells
for and blue skirt sold for 2 49 so that
seems pretty good we'll pop the blue
skirt in for 249 how much we looking at
from those 7K from that as well now we
only been doing this for 10 minutes and
we made about 15K so per hour that's
about
75k not bad from an initial cash deck
perspective anyway we'll go ahead and
inst sell these we might not continue
buying these capes because they don't
seem to be that
good uh but that being said we do have
enough money now oh wow they only sold
for three that was a mistake uh we'll
pop these in here for 49 maybe and hope
uh that they sell so now we have uh 15K
now we're only going to need about 2k of
that because we're going to be going
into the Wilderness and buying a team
Cape now we've gone ahead and looked at
all the team capes and looks like the
cape
11 uh seems to be the most valuable all
right so we decided to just open up G
tracker here and actually it looks like
the team Cape 22 might be going for the
most at this current price of course we
do have to take into account whether or
not it's actually going to sell it all I
mean these probably don't trade very
much every day but even if we could sell
a couple for 4K that would be
amazing and these only trade 51 a day I
mean that's not that bad and they've
been selling for uh between 500 and 1200
okay that's not very good let's have a
look at the rest of them team Cape 11
was the one I had originally looked at
Cape
11 there we go so the cape 11 let's have
a look at this one looks like it's up to
book 2.5k and
1.7k uh trades 73 a day we'll go ahead
to the furthest team cape shop anyway
and go ahead and buy from him we'll just
buy a couple capes and see what ends up
working the best so uh well we'll grab
the money here and grab about 2k and
we'll go see if we can find the dude cuz
he wanders around a lot all right guys
so we're in the deepest of wilderness
for free to play we're between the
Demonic runes and the lava dragon Al and
we finally find William uh the [__] back
here man he is pretty annoying to find
usually but here he is here's uh the
team capes now we're going for the team
Cape 11 uh so each five we buy cost uh
well 250 coins 10 C 10 cost 50 we'll
drop our jugs of wine cuz well we
shouldn't need them anymore can't drop
them anymore
actually ah where'd you go to William
anyway we got the capes we're going to
run back to the gr change and hopefully
we don't die on the way all right guys
we me the back alive unfortunately the
[__] idiot ran away and we couldn't
actually get any more capes but that's
okay we'll go ahead and we're going to
start just by dumping one see how much
we
could um no wait what are we doing here
uh we'll go
bot let's just try it selling one and
seeing what we can actually sell it for
so team Cape
11 and we'll see if it sells for $
8.91 sold for 3410
H all right well we'll put the rest of
those in I'm totally happy with that
3410 3410 so that one trip took us
about 20 minutes and it looks like we
might actually get 75k from that uh we
sold four so far but we'll leave that in
there for now uh and I think we're going
to go ahead and buy some more capes do a
couple more runs and we probably will
diversify The Capes a bit but these team
Cape 11s assuming they sell reasonably
quickly I might go ahead and buy more of
those all right we'll be back when uh we
get more capes all right one mad dash
for the Wilderness later well actually
two and we have returned we did not die
and uh we managed to get more team cap
11s uh now it's been about half an hour
it took us about half an hour to do two
runs we got really lucky one of the
times the second time not so much uh so
we'll withraw all the team cap 11s we
decided to just go with the team cap 11
because as we were doing the Run uh they
actually all sold for 3410 uh which is
insan we'll go ahead collect all that
that 64k I we'll pop these into sell
again for about 3410 sounds good 3410 so
hopefully those sell soon that's
177k now our plan now is to we'll get
all our money out so we have about 100K
and it's been an hour not so good but
again that is starting from a blank cash
tag so not awful in the gram scheme of
things we are going to start off by
training our magic because we do want
telekinetic grab pretty soon because we
are going to be telegrabbing uh nature
runes in the wilderness and that
requires 33 magic and uh yes we'll start
off by buy some runes we can only do I
guess we're level eight so that's going
to be Earth strike I guess no water
strike buy an an air staff to begin with
here staff of
air we need one of those and then we're
going to need some fire runes
uh sorry mind runes and then like a
little bit of water runes a little bit
Earth runes and some fire
runes so mind runes we'll go
for
thousand casts probably reasonable for
now and then we're going to need some
water
runes couple hundred of those maybe 300
that's probably too much Earth
runes little more
those again that's probably way too much
we'll just go for
200 and uh we'll need some fire
runes fire runes we're going to buy
quite a few CU we'll need a lot of those
we'll go
for uh just a thousand just a rough
estimate to get some magic levels in
we're going to start working on 33 while
these items sell and before we do that
one other thing I want to prep is um
something I've done in the past is you
buy mithil plate
bodies and uh now they sell to horvik's
armor shop here we got a little notepad
open here for 3210 and the steel one
cell for 1,200 not sure if I'm going to
do the studed chaps they seem to be
worth it but these seem to be buying for
roughly uh we'll buy and sell one just
to see 2447 or
2947 and they're selling for
2880 so we'll go ahead buy some of these
20 for now steel plate
bodies also seem to work pretty well
we'll buy and sell those uh so they buy
for
1080 and sell
for 108 I guess that's worth it and
we'll do some of these as well all right
guys we'll come back with some magic
levels all right there is level 14 magic
uh we just came over here to goblins
this is pretty much what I always do
when I start a new account
and level up my magic so there's 14 it's
all we really need for now I can't do
that now we can use fire strike which is
nice and I think uh we're going to go to
Hill Giants cuz they can drop Lim Roots
which are worth some money so we might
as well do that uh but first uh if you
have a look at our um chat here we
bought all the mythal blade bodies we'll
go ahead and just check if this is going
to be viable cuz off of 20 plate bodies
we'd
make 4k on each 10 10 8K off the myths
maybe 5K off of the
Steels 13k it's not a lot of work I'm
not sure if it's actually worth doing
but we'll go ahead sell those off and
then go to the hill Giants all right the
plate bodies was a terrible idea don't
do it it's a pain in the ass and it
ended up breaking even pretty well uh so
we're going to head off to Hill Giants
we're still waiting for our um Team cap
cell they are steadily coming through
and we do have 27k lined up there which
is pretty awesome one thing I did notice
is the staff of fires actually have a
really good margin on them uh so we'll
put an offer in for well close to 100 by
close I mean exactly 100 and we got the
runes to kill some fire Giants and we'll
be off and back when uh the flips in all
right guys there's level 20 magic uh the
levels are coming pretty quick we're
getting about 20K experience an hour
here we only need about 15K to get to
level 33 uh one of the only benefits of
the worlds being disconnecting all the
time is uh that there are not that many
people here so that's a plus and Yeah we
actually bought all the staffs of fire
as well and sold a bit more of those
team capes uh but yeah we'll just we'll
just grind out 33 and uh unless all the
team cape sell in which case we might go
do something else um but for now we're
just going to grind out 33 and uh be
back then all right guys there is 33
magic just finish it up quickly for you
and now we can use telekinetic grab
which will be useful uh for when we're
going to be uh telegrabbing the nature
runes one could also telegrab wi of ZX
but while I was doing this I had look on
my alt and there's just a shitload of
people there in the free to play World
so we're probably not going to do that
uh conveniently also we have the
teleports unlocked which will come in
handy uh that being said we are down to
about over 2 hours and 15 minutes about
is how far we're in and let's go a look
at our grand exchange quickly okay so
for the grand exchange all of our staffs
of Fire have bought which is nice we'll
go ahead and just resell those
quickly staff of fire not sure how much
money we'll make off this but I think at
least 10K 873 yeah so those in there for
872 so we are selling them for 88k and
we bought them for 70k so 18K in profit
pretty good for the money we invested
we've also sold above 24 of these team
caves so we have about 100K left there
and we'll go ahead and dump the rest of
these items in a second so now what
we're going to be doing is going fairly
deep into the
Wilderness to the where is it now it's
right here right south of the Demonic
runes there are two nature run spawns
one for three nature runes and one for
four nature runes that you can telegrab
and just bring runes they stackable
items so you can stay here as long as
you want it is a little bit risky
because of the location but I'm going to
risk it and yeah so we're going to take
uh well I calculated it out you'll need
about 42k to do this for an hour and we
have 100 so that should be good we'll do
it for 1 hour and we'll show you where
it is and get it start started and then
we'll do it for an hour see how much we
make probably repeat it a couple times
assuming we don't get killed all right
we'll meet you out there all right guys
we are in the Deep Wilderness if you
don't know where this is it is literally
the top right corner of the map pretty
much right by the Demonic run just a
little bit South now this is one of the
deepest areas you can go in free to play
but there's two interesting spawns here
naturon and naturon so all we have to do
is uh telegrab the
one telegrab the other
and the new hop worlds now this is
actually more money per hour than
telegrabbing wines of zamra way less
crowded because it's in the wilderness
and um especially since again the
servers are very bad right now I mean
like who would have thought there
wouldn't be uh freeo playay deep wiy
pees at this hour but yeah know it looks
pretty clear to me and yeah we're just
going to go ahead um telegrab the Rune
telegrab the other one hop takes about
15 seconds seconds and we get seven
nature runes every 15 seconds we'll
calculate the profit after and we'll
probably Bank after an hour all right
we'll be back in a bit all right well
that was pretty much a success we are
just about to escape the Wilderness we
did about an hour uh pretty much on the
dot we used all our runes uh 1747 is
what we ended up getting oh God what is
that um and we're just about to teleport
over here we have one Rune left for the
teleport which is uh pretty smart and
get us the [__] out of here perfect
so we escaped with 1747 runes it cost us
about 50 80k for so it's first 440 so
that's really good I would go as far to
say that this is possibly the best money
per hour that you can get in free to
play uh but of course someone could be
open to contest me on that but I have
not yet found a method that is better
than this uh so far so we'll head to the
Grand exchange and uh see how much we
actually bought those l runes for and
how much we actually profited from the
hour assuming it's all good we're
probably going to grind this out for a
couple hours cuz the plan is to get a
cash attack maybe 1 to 1.5 mil and then
do some flipping for the last M or two
hopefully only one anyway we're back at
the Grand exchange let's go ahead and
sell these nature runes
off we're lazy we're going to sell them
right away so we sold them for
435k and we bought them for about 888k
so it's about 350k profit every hour so
I think this is very good uh I didn't
get killed it went very smoothly we'll
see if the next hour does uh a similar
amount and yeah we'll go uh try to
repeat this okay I don't think I can
handle any more of that we managed to
survive but oh my god there wasn't that
many people there but the three times I
think someone logged in and tried to
attack me one successfully did attack me
I had a Runway uh I didn't restock my
wines but oh my God that was that was a
little bit too much for me I don't think
I'm going to be doing too much more of
that but we did do the full two hours
we're down to about 6
hours um sorry not down but we're into
the challenge about 6 hours and pretty
happy I think uh we were going to make
about 600k from that we'll probably have
close to a m now and that's going to be
plenty to start flipping and uh maybe
we'll go by from the Rune shop in verac
as well then a little bit safer and
still get about 200k an hour doing that
and and yeah we'll just run quickly to
the Grand exchange sell these off and
just see how much uh cash we have at the
moment so if we withdraw the 273k we
have in the
bank and sell off now these team cap 11s
haven't been selling very quick but
uh oh not these sell off the nature
runes that's going to be about
850k perfect so our cash Shack is
looking at about 1127 we're going to
have to readjust these prices but we'll
go ahead and put some flips in for you
guys
all right so now we can move on to my
favorite part which is flipping now the
team cap 11s did end up selling uh we
got another 111k coming from that uh the
staffs of fire we just ended up dumping
so they weren't really going anywhere
that leaves us with 1.3 mil pretty well
half of the way there and we have three
offer slots so we'll just do the best we
can so we're going to start with the
Rune armor set SKS uh we're going to buy
them for
500 and uh we'll go
for five of those we want to leave
enough money is that going to be
enough not quite we're going to go for
four of those uh we're going to also try
to buy a guilded chain body run armor
set
SK 138 500 and just four of those uh we
just have a quick look at some of these
items on GT tracker looks like 138 into
14 9 pretty good uh the Gilla chain
body not as good but that's still a 30k
margin which I think might still be
worth it so we'll go ahead and put our
offering for the Gilded chain body as
well hit about
672k and then yeah we're going to have
to wait for these flips to come in we'll
probably use our 85k to go buy Rune
packs while we're waiting and that will
come back when the items have sold
all right so now what we're doing is
buying Rune packs out of arber's Rune
shop now the reason I didn't do this
before is because it's really click
intensive but the actual money is very
good uh so you can see you can click
through all them very quickly and uh
since you can sell air runes and fire
runes for um five coins each and the air
packs are worth
430 roughly so opening them up gives you
500 coins worth of runes and since you
can open up runes like pretty quick each
one is worth 50k or 50 coins you can be
the whole inventory is worth like a 1.5k
or something you can do it very quickly
but again you're clicking a shitload
which I don't like as much uh but yeah
we're just doing that while our items
are selling and buying looks like we've
bought in all the items we're going to
head back to the Grand
exchange all right good news everybody
we have sold the guilded chain body for
a astounding profit of 100K we sold it
for 760 and we bought it for6
72 uh oh almost 100K 90k is still
extremely good so we're going to go
ahead and buy another one of those for
sure uh the Gilded or the Rune armor
sets have almost all sold and uh we have
some air runes to sell off as well I
think we're going to keep this cash to
buy air runes while we just flip this
gild of chain body because these
actually are slower than I thought and
we will need an offer slot available
anyway and uh yeah pretty happy so far
we'll come back with some more flips I
okay we have another gilded chain body
flip coming in for another 90k uh we did
just dump off the other Rune armor set
because it wasn't going anywhere and on
top of that we did put an offer in for
the Rune
Scimitar uh not a huge margin on it only
500 GP but we're going for 30 right now
surpris none have boughten actually but
that's okay definitely going to put
another offer in for this gilded chain
body which isn't even on here
anymore gilded chain body
at
668k and do one of those and we'll pop
these into to sell here need to sell
eventually and we're getting pretty
close to the 8 hour mark uh
now yeah we're doing pretty well I think
my goal is to get
under I guess 12 hours now I'm not sure
if we're going to hit that but we're
going to try our best and we'll see uh
you with the next flips
all right I really don't want to do this
but I'm kind of tired of just waiting
around for offers to complete uh so
we're going to head into the Wilderness
again and do more of the telegraphing uh
we're going to go for another 2 hours
we're going to bring uh 1,000 law runes
roughly and we should have enough of
that perfect all right so we'll take the
law runes come back when any of our
major offers have completed and
hopefully I don't get killed okay so
we're approaching the 10hour Mark
actually I think we're past it and uh we
have one guilded chain body flip so
another 100K there and we're just about
to get another one coming in as well uh
for another 100K which is pretty awesome
again there was almost nobody at the uh
nature room spawn except for the the
second hour that we did it there's like
one person chasing me around but beyond
that not too much uh gilded or run SAR
flip coming in
for 20K
uh not as good as the other ones by any
means and we have a bunch of nature
runes now this is going to bring us
pretty damn close
2153 and uh with this money ooh 2366 I
don't think we can afford a bond for
that much we'll give it a try 23
66k
no okay we're going to have to do a
couple more flips here and then we
should finally have enough for Bond uh
we're only at the 10hour Mark so I think
we can get it before 12 uh which was my
goal and uh yeah let's get to
it okay so we're back with another
gilded chain body flip among others uh
but that one was definitely the best
again I'm not going to be flipping this
item anymore so if you want to give it a
try uh it did have 100K margin when I
was doing it uh we also did kind of a
messy flip on the cosmic runes I we lost
money or broke even on that uh death
runes we ended up getting about a 40 or
50k profit on uh which is pretty decent
so we have 254
4K I'm going to see if we can buy a bond
with that much I think we might be able
to anything in the
bank no all right let's see if we can
buy an old school bond for 25 for 4K
come
on there it is guys the bond has been
purchased so the timer can wow well we
actually overkilled it
now timer can be stopped so uh we were
counting that from 24 hours so we pretty
much did it
in 11
hours so that that's an hour under what
I was hoping to do it in so I'm pretty
happy with how that went and now that we
have the bond I have decided that we're
going to give the bond away so all you
have to do to enter this giveaway is
leave a comment with why you want the
bond or what you're going to do with the
bond once you have it make sure to like
the video and uh subscribe to my channel
and I will pick a random winner uh
sometime this week and yeah for any of
you who actually stuck through this
whole thing appreciate it and uh yeah
I'll see you guys in the next video
[Music]